It's true that assembly AI lets you build powerful apps with voice
data, but is voice really the right word? Maybe
words, but words on their own are just that, words.
Audio, we hear you. The hearing is
just a fraction of it. Stack it up and you
might get closer. But it's more than what we can
see or hear. It's something in between, around
and beneath all of that speech.
Speech is more than what you say, it's what you mean. And
more than the data. The models and. The benchmarks. That's
what we're excited by at Assembly, AI meaning.
And all of the possibilities that come with it. It's
why we've built industry leading AI models for speech to
text and speech understanding. They give you richer. Data,
incredible accuracy and deeper understanding
so you can get to the meaning behind voice data and.
Build products that are more than just. Powerful, they're
meaningful.