We're no strangers to love you
know the rules and so do I. I
feel commitments while I'm thinking of you
wouldn' get this from any other guy
I just want to tell you how I'm
feeling Gotta make you
understand Never gonna give you up never
gonna let you down Never gonna run around
and desert you Never gonna
make you cry Never gonna say goodbye
Never gonna tell a lie and hurt
you We've known your
heart's been aching but you're too shy to
say it inside we both know what's been going
on we know the game and we're
gonna play it and if
you ask me how I feeling don't
tell me you're too blind to see Never gonna
give you up never gonna let you down
Never gonna run around and desert
you Never gonn Never
gonna say goodbye Never gonna tell a
fight and hurt you Never
gonna give you up never gonna let you
down Never gonna run around and
desert you Never gonna make you
cry Never gonna say goodbye Never
gonna tell a l Never
gonna give Never gonna give Never
gonna give Never gonna give We've
known each other for so long your
heart's been aching but you're too shy to
say it's sad we both know what's been going
on. We know the game and we're
gonna play it. I just
wanna tell you how I'm feel understand
Never gonna give you up never gonna let
you down Never gonna run around and
desert you Never gonna make you
cry I'm gonna say goodbye Never
gonna tell a lie and hurt you
Never gonna give you up never gonna let
you down Never gonna run around and
desert you Never gonna make you
cry Never gon tell
a lie and hurt you Never
going to give you up Never going to let you
down Never going to run around and
desert you Never going to make you
cry Never going to say goodbye Never
going to.